各位请安静,中央公园很荣幸为各位介绍
Everybody! Central Perk is proud to present...
…菲比布菲小姐的音乐
...the music of Miss Phoebe Buffay.
谢谢，
Thanks.
首先我想从一首...
I wanna start with a song that's about that moment...
有关顿悟人生那一刻的歌…开始
...when you suddenly realize what life is really all about.
开始...
Okay,here we go.
非常感谢
Okay. Thank you very much.
什么?这下可…
Oh,great. This is just
六人行 第1季 第07集 纽约大停电
The One With The Blackout
这简直是酷毙了 纽约大停电
This is so cool,you guys. The entire city's blacked out.
我妈说是整个布鲁克林 部分曼哈顿和皇后区
It's all of Manhattan. They have no idea...
不知何时恢复电力
...when it's back on.
-这可真是大停电 -裤子和毛衣,为什么,妈?
-You guys,this is big. -Pants and a sweater. Why,Mom?
停电我能去见谁?
Who will I meet in a blackout?
电力公司的人? 单身的趁火打劫之徒?
Power-company guys? Eligible looters?
-以后再聊，好吗? -电话能借我吗?
-Can we talk about this later? Okay. -Can I borrow the phone?
我想打回住处 确定我祖母是否安好
I wanna call my apartment and check on my grandma.
等等，我的电话几号?
What's my number?
我从未打电话给自己过
I never call me.
天啊，是她 维多利亚的秘密(内衣品牌)的模特儿
Oh,my God! It's her. It's that Victoria 's Secret model.
叫什么古亚克的
Something Goodacre.
妈，我是洁儿
Hi,Mom,it's Jill.
没错，洁儿 洁儿・古亚克 天哪!
She 's right. It's Jill. Jill Goodacre. Oh,my God!
没想到我和洁儿.古亚克同时被困在提款机室
I am trapped in an A TM vestibule with Jill Goodacre.
是小室还是正厅?
Is it a vestibule? Maybe it's an atrium.
那才是值得注意的部分，笨蛋
Yeah,that is the part to focus on,you idiot.
对，我没事只是被困在银行提款机室
I' m fine. I' m just stuck at the bank in an ATM vestibule.
洁儿说小室? 那我也说小室
Jill says vestibule,I'm going with vestibule.
我没事,不,旁边有人
I' m fine. No,l' m not alone.
我不认识,某人
I don't know,some guy.
某人?某人
Oh,some guy. I am some guy.
洁儿，我昨晚看见你和某人在一起
Jill,I saw you with some guy last night.
没错，他是某人.
Yes,he was some guy.
各位
Hey,everyone.
（犹太人光明节的传统象征）
今晚主持停电晚会的 是犹太教士崔比安尼
Officiating at tonight's blackout is Rabbi T ribbiani.
钱德的老室友是个犹太人 我们只剩这些蜡烛
Chandler's old roommate was Jewish. These are our only candles.
祝各位光明节快乐
So happy Hanukkah!
瞧，丑陋裸男点燃了几根蜡烛
Look! Ugly Naked Guy lit a bunch of candles.
一定很痛
That had to hurt!
已过了14分30秒
All right,all right! It's been 14 1/2 minutes...
…你却连一字也没说
...and you still haven 't said one word. God!
争气点，打破沉闷，微笑
Do something! Just make contact. Smile!
效果不错
There you go.
算了吧，你正在吓她
You 're definitely scaring her.
喂? 妈妈.
Hello? Oh,hi,Mom.
妈.
Mom.
妈妈,你在嗑药!
Mom,you' re tripping!
德特是一条狗 大停电把他吓坏了
Dexter's a dog. The blackout's scaring him.
如果你不知道 你也可以尿在爸爸的鞋子里.
You'd pee in Dad's shoes too if you didn't know.
好吧，给我回电话
All right,call me back.
-是妈妈. -是的.
-Mothers. -Yeah.
好小伙!一个词.
Attaboy! A word.
这样不坏.妈妈，是的！
That wasn 't so hard. Mothers. Yeah!
妈妈，是的！完美
Mothers. Yeah! Perfect.
不要笑.
Don 't smile.
你需要给别人打电话吗?
Would you like to call somebody?
是的，和我一起上高中的300个小伙
Yeah,about 300 guys I went to high school with.
是的，谢了.
Yeah,thanks.
-你好? -是我
-Hello? -It's me.
-是钱德,你好吗? -我还好
-It's Chandler. Are you okay? -Yeah,l' m fine.
我被困在提款机室...
I' m stuck in an ATM vestibule...
和洁儿吉亚克一起
...with Jill Goodacre.
-什么? -我被困在...
-What? -l' m stuck...
...提款机室了...
...in an ATM vestibule...
...和洁儿吉亚克一起
...with Jill Goodacre.
我听不懂你在说什么
I have no idea what you said.
叫乔伊听电话
Put Joey on the phone.
-怎么了? -我被困在...
-What's up,man? -l' m stuck...
...提款机室了...
...in an ATM vestibule...
...和洁儿吉亚克一起
...with Jill Goodacre!
噢,我的天那
Oh,my God!
他和洁儿吉亚克被困在提款机室
He's trapped in an ATM vestibule with Jill Goodacre!
钱德，听着…
Chandler,listen.
别以为我没这个念头
Like that thought never entered my mind.
换人，快
-Okay. -Somebody.
好吧，换我
-I'll go. I'll go. -Okay.
大四在桌球台上
Senior year of college,on a pool table.
-桌球台上? -这就是我妹啦
-Pool table? -That's my sister.
我最奇怪的地方是在...
Okay,my weirdest place would have to be...
...纽约市立图书馆二楼女厕
...the women's room of the New York City Public Library.
拜托，你去图书馆干什么
Oh,my God! What were you doing in a library?
-菲比，你呢? -密尔沃基市(威斯康星州)
-Pheebs,what about you? -Oh,Milwaukee.
真是一个奇怪的地方.
It's a really weird place.
罗斯?
Ross?
迪士尼，1989年小小世界
Disneyland,1 989. " It's a small world after all. "
不可能…
No way.
机器故障
The ride broke down...
所以我和卡萝就到荷兰机器儿童后面
...so Carol and I went behind those mechanical Dutch children.
从此他们禁止我们再到奇幻王国去
We were asked never to return to the Magic Kingdom.
好吧,还剩下…
Let's see,that leaves....
-瑞秋? -拜托，我说过了
-Rachel? -Come on,I already went.
-你才没哪 -我说过了
-You did not go. -I did.
快点告诉我们
T ell us. Come on.
好吧，最奇怪的地方是...
All right,the weirdest place would have to be...
...床脚
...the foot of the bed.
-真没意义 -我们有优胜了
-Step back! -We have a winner!
这就是冰箱关上时候的样子
This must be what the fridge looks like with the door closed.
恐怖.
Spooky.
有人饿了吗?我们有科隆迪克冰激凌…汤
Anybody hungry? We got a Klondike...soup.
我从来没有那种关系也没那种感受
I've never had a relationship with that kind of passion.
在主题乐园中你忽然欲火中烧
Where you have to have somebody even in a theme park.
当时只有这件事可做
It was the only thing to do that didn't have a line.
贝瑞连在打迷你高尔夫时 也不肯亲我
Barry wouldn't even kiss me on a miniature golf course.
-不是吧 -是的
-Come on. -No.
他说这样会耽误后面的人
He said we held up the people behind us.
你逃婚的原因是…
You didn't marry him because...?
你认为有人这辈子没有过那种…
Do you think there are people that go through life...
…从来没有过…
... never having that kind of...?
-也许吧. -真的?
-Probably. -Really?
但是我得告诉你 激情被过度重视.
I'll tell you something. Passion is way overrated.
-没错 -是的
-Yeah,right. -lt is.
最后激情很快就退去
Eventually,it kind of burns out.
但双方仍保有信赖，安全感和...
But hopefully what you're left with is trust and security and....
以我前妻为例…女同志主义
In my ex-wife's case,lesbianism.
因此,缺乏激情之人还是有…
For those people who miss out on that passion thing...
…其他可取之处的
...there's other stuff.
但我想你不是那种人
-Okay. -But I don't think that'll be you.
-你认为我不是? -我认为...
-You don't? -See,I see...
-你的未来将充满激情 -真的?
-... big passion in your future. -Really?
-你真的这样认为 -没错
-You do? -I do.
罗斯，你真好
Ross,you' re so great.
不可能发生的
It's never gonna happen.
-什么? -你和瑞秋
-What? -You and Rachel.
为什么?
Why not?
因为你拖太久才行动
You waited too long to make your move...
现在只能待在“朋友区”
...and now you' re in the "friend zone. "
-不，我没在朋友区 -罗斯，你是朋友区主席
-l' m not in the zone. -No,Ross. You' re mayor of the zone.
我在静观其变，行吗? 我正在为以后铺路
Look,l' m taking my time,all right? I' m laying the groundwork.
我每天往前推进一点
Every day I get a little bit closer to
圣人
Priesthood!
告诉你,罗斯,她根本不知道你在想什么
I'm telling you,she has no idea what you're thinking.
她刚刚用她的手指缕我的头发.
She just ran her fingers through my hair.
-你没看到那个互动吗? -不,不,不.
-Were you missing that interaction? -No,no,no.
这才是缕你的头发.
This is running fingers through your hair,okay?
这不过是弄乱你的头发罢了.
Now this is a tousle.
如果再不快点约她出去 你将困在朋友区永远无法脱身
If you don't ask her out soon,you'll be in the zone forever.
我会的 我只是在等恰当的时机
I will,I will. I'm waiting for the right moment.
什么?
What?
-什么,现在? -是的.
-What,now? -Yeah.
你缺什么? 美酒?烛光?月光?
What's messing you up? The wine? The moonlight?
你只需走到她面前说 瑞秋，我想你…
You gotta go up to her and say," Look,Rachel,l"
-什么? -我们在嘘…
-What? -We' re shushing...
…因为我们正在听
... because we' re trying to hear something.
-什么？ -难道你没听见?
-What? What? -Don't you hear that?
听见没?
See?
-想来片口香糖吗? -无糖的吗?
-Would you like gum? -ls it sugarless?
-抱歉，不是 -不，谢了
-Sorry,it's not. -Then no,thanks.
你在搞什么东西?
What was that?
切记!洁儿请你吃口香糖你就吃
Mental note: If Jill Goodacre offers you gum,you take it.
她叫你吃动物死尸 你也得吃
If she offers you mangled animal carcass,you take it!
纽约大停电
New York City has no power
牛奶变酸
And the milk is getting sour
不过没关系
But to me it is not scary
因为我不喝牛奶
Because I stay away from dairy
-你决定啦? -我决定了
-Here goes. -You'll do it?
-我决定了 -需要帮助吗?
-I'll do it. -Want help?
如果你出现你就死定了
You come out,you' re a dead man.
--罗斯…祝你幸运 -谢谢.
-Good luck,man. -Thanks.
好了
-Okay.
你要去哪里? 外面 不行，你不能去外面
Where you going? You can't go out there.
-为什么? -因为有理由
-Why not? -Because of the reason.
-那是什么? -不能告诉你
-That would be? -I can't tell you.
乔伊，到底怎么了?
Joey,what's going on?
好吧，但你得答应我 不会告诉罗斯是我说的
You gotta promise you'll never tell Ross that I told you.
-说什么? -他正在准备你的生日舞会
-What? -He's planning your birthday party.
-天啊，我爱他 -你最好装成一副吃惊的样子
-Oh,my God! I love him! -You better act surprised.
-装什么? -我的生日舞会
-About what? -My surprise party.
-什么生日舞会? -少装蒜了,乔伊已经告诉我了
-What surprise party? -Oh,stop it. Joey already told me.
他没有告诉我
He didn't tell me.
别看我，这是罗斯的主意
Don't look at me. This is Ross' thing.
每次都这样,我总是最后知道的人
This is typical. I'm always the last to know.
你不是，我们都有告诉你哦
You are not. We tell you stuff.
钱德在动物园被孔雀咬 我是最后知道的人
I was the last one to know when Chandler got bit by the peacock.
也是最后知道乔伊刚搬来时 你对他有意思的人
I was the last to know you had a crush on Joey.
什么?
What?
看来我是倒数第二
Looks like I was second to last.
你对我有意思?
You had a crush on me?
好吧,这不算是有意思,是有点印象.
All right. It wasn't a crush,it was a dent.
很深的印象?
Big dent?
你搬了我的家具 我想你的胳膊不错,仅此而已.
You were moving your furniture. I thought you had nice arms.
胳膊不错?
Nice arms,huh?
嘿,莫妮卡,我在搬动椅子哦.
Hey,Mon,l' m moving the chair.
你感觉怎么样？
Do anything for you?
所有的灯都灭了,你才可以真正的看到星星啊.
With all the lights out you can actually see the stars.
真不错.
It's so nice.
我有个问题
I have a question.
也谈不上是问题
Actually,it's not so much a question.
只是…
It's more of a general wondering....
好奇.
ment.
-好吧 -好吧,是这样的.
-Okay. -Okay. Here it goes.
这些日子以来我一直想…
Well,for a while now,I've been wanting to....
-对，没错 -瞧那只小猫!
-Yes,that's right. -Look at that little kitty!
什么?
What?
我在世界万物之上俯身看尘世
Top of the world Looking down on creation
我发现唯一能够解释这一切的
And the only explanation I can find
是爱，自从有你在身旁
Is the love that I found Ever since you 've been around
好吧,这只是洗伤口的药不会痛的
All right,this is just Bactine. It won't hurt.
-噢! -对不起，是蜡油
-Ow! -Sorry,that was wax.
可怜的小猫快吓死了 我们得找到它的主人
Poor little T ooty's scared. We should find his owner.
何不将它放在走廊?
Why not put poor T ooty in the hall?
大停电时?它会被踩死的
During a blackout? She'll get trampled.
是吗?
Yeah?
亡羊补牢.回到口香糖的话题
Damage control. Get back to the gum.
口香糖是绝佳的选择
Gum would be perfection.
口香糖是绝佳的选择?
Gum would be perfection?
口香糖是绝佳的选择
Gum would be perfection.
我大可说“口香糖不错”,但不，
Could've said,"Gum would be nice. " But,no.
我说的是"口香糖是绝佳的选择"
For me,gum is perfection.
我真鄙视我自己
I loathe myself!
不，她们是修女,讨厌一切生物
Oh,no,they' re nuns. They hate all living things.
我们刚捡到这只猫 目前正在找它的主人
Hi. We just found this cat,and we' re looking for the owner.
猫是我的
Yeah,it's mine.
-可是它似乎很讨厌你 -确定，猫是我的，把猫给我
-He seems to hate you. Are you sure? -It's my cat. Give me my cat.
-等等，它叫什么名字? -鲍伯钮扣
-Wait a minute. What's his name? -Bob Buttons.
--鲍伯钮扣? -鲍伯钮扣,过来,鲍伯钮扣
-Bob Buttons? -Bob Buttons. Here,Bob Buttons.
你真是个大坏蛋
You are a very bad man!
你们欠我一只猫
You owe me a cat.
来这,咪咪,咪咪,咪咪.
Here,kitty,kitty,kitty.
Here,kitty,kitty.
小猫咪…你上哪儿去了?
Where did you go,little kitty?
小猫咪,过来.
Kitty,kitty,kitty. Come here,kitty,kitty.
-嗨 -晚上好 (意大利语)
-Hi. -Buona sera.
喔!
Wow!
莫妮卡,愿意搭我的跑车去兜风吗?
Mon,wanna go for a ride in my racecar?
我会带我的胳膊一起去的.
I'll bring my arms.
我们为你的牙齿准备独轮车!
We can bring my wheelbarrow for your teeth!
来吧，幸运六
Come on,lucky sixes!
各位，他是保罗
Everybody,this is Paolo.
保罗，向你介绍我的朋友 这位是莫妮卡
Paolo,I want you to meet my friends. This is Monica...
-嗨-…这位是乔伊…
-Hi. -...and Joey...
-嗨 -…还有罗斯…
-Hi. -...and Ross.
嗨
Hi.
他不太会讲英语
He doesn't speak much English.
大富翁
Monopoly!
看啊!
Look at that!
那,保罗来自哪里?
So,where did Paolo come from?
我猜是意大利
Italy,I think.
不，我是指今晚,这栋公寓? 突然介入我们的生活?
No,I mean tonight. Suddenly,into our lives.
那只猫结果是保罗的 这不是很有意思吗?
That cat turned out to be Paolo's cat. Isn't that funny?
真有意思,而且瑞秋不断摸他
That is funny. And Rachel keeps touching him.
我找遍了整栋公寓,但就是找不到猫
I looked all over and couldn't find the kitty anywhere.
我找到了，是保罗的猫
I found him. It was Paolo's cat.
瞧，我又是最后一个知道
Well,there you go. Last to know again.
由于没人告诉我,我猜他就是保罗
And I'm guessing,this is Paolo?
保罗，她叫菲比
Paolo,this is Phoebe.
当然了
You betcha!
好吧,下一步呢?
All right. Okay. What next?
吹泡泡,吹泡泡不错.
Blow a bubble. A bubble's good.
可以很好展现男性魅力，顽皮的一面
It's got a boyish charm. It's impish.
来吧
Here we go.
吹得可真好，小鬼
Nice going,imp!
不要紧,我只需把手伸过去
It's okay. All I need to do...
将它放回口中
...is reach over and put it back in my mouth.
救得好,现在我已重回轨道
Good save! We 're back on track and I'm...
而且还嚼著别人的口香糖
... chewing someone else 's gum.
这不是我的口香糖,天哪,我的天啊!
This is not my gum! Oh,my God! Oh,my God!
很好,现在你呛到了
And now you 're choking.
你没事吧
You all right?
天呀,你呛到了
My God! You' re choking!
-感觉好点没? -好多了
-Better? -Yes.
谢谢，那真是…
Thank you. That was....
-那真是… -绝佳的选择?
-That was.... -Perfection?
这可不是把头发弄乱而已
That was no tousle.
-他讲什么这么好笑 -我完全搞不懂
-What'd he say that was so funny? -I have absolutely no idea.
女人都这样
That's classic.
天啊，我在干什么? 这太不像我了
My God,you guys! What am I doing? This is so un-me!
不介意的话我要上了
If you want,I'll do it.
我只想咬他的下嘴唇
I just wanna bite his bottom lip.
但我不会这么做的
But I won't.
他第一次对我微笑时
The first time he smiled at me...
那三秒钟比我和贝瑞 在百慕达的三个礼拜还令我兴奋
...those seconds were more exciting than weeks with Barry.
你们租脚踏车了吗?
Did you rent mopeds?
因为我听说…我离题了
Because I've heard Oh,it's not about that right now.
我知道这样很肤浅 而且我们毫无共通点
I know it's superficial,and we have nothing in common...
连语言也不通但...上帝啊
...and we don't even speak the same language,but,God!
-保罗 -罗斯
-Paolo,hi. -Ross.
听着
Listen....
有件事你该了解
Listen,something you should know.
瑞秋和我
Rachel and I are....
有那么一点
We' re kind of a thing.
-一点? -一点.是的,一点
-Thing? -Thing. Yes,thing.
-你们做爱没有？ -没有.
-You have the sex? -No.
技术上而言，还没做爱
No,technically the sex is not being had. But that's....
但这不是重点
But that's not the point.
重点是瑞秋和我应该…
The point is that Rachel and I should be....
瑞秋和我应该在一起
Well,Rachel and l should be together.
如果你来到
And if you get in the
-床上? -不是
-ln bed -No.
不是，我不是指那个
No,not where I was going.
如果你来到我们中间掺合
If you get in the way of us becoming a thing...
我会非常…难过
...then I would be,well,very sad.
所以,你…
So,do you...?
-你懂一点英文？ -会一点
-So you do know a little English? -Little.
-你懂什么叫“人渣”吗 -不懂
-Do you know the word "crap-weasel "? -No.
不懂?真好笑 因为你就是个超级人渣
That's funny. You are a huge crap-weasel.
我们玩了一小时,很简单的
We've been doing this for an hour. It's easy.
准备好没?
Ready?
试试看
Okay? Now try it.
不，你该拍一下
You gotta whip it.
看，最后一根蜡烛就要燃尽
Look,look. The last candle's about to burn out.
10，9，8，7
Ten,nine,eight,seven...
负46，负47，负48…
... minus 46,minus 47,minus 48....
-谢谢 -谢谢
-Thank you. -Thanks.
没有灯光有点恐怖
Kind of spooky without any lights.
停，我这个最逼真
Okay,guys,I have the definitive one.
罗斯，现在提并不恰当
This probably isn't the best time to bring it up...
但你得为莫妮卡开个派对
...but you have to throw a party for Monica.
-玩得真开心 -对
-This has been fun. -Yes.
谢谢你的手机
Thanks for letting me use your phone...
并救了我的命
...and for saving my life.
再见了，钱德 此次停电我玩得很开心
Well,goodbye,Chandler. I had a great blackout.
再见
See you.
我的帐号是7143457
Hi,l' m account number 7143457.
我不知道你们有没有录下来
I don't know if you got that...
但我想要这卷录影带的拷贝
... but I would really like a copy of the tape.